https://cottey.edu/policies-and-privacy/

GiveStudentsAlumnaeP.E.O.
Cottey College, Website Privacy PolicyCottey College is committed to protecting the privacy of confidential information submitted by website visitors. The following document discloses the public privacy rights of Cottey College website visitors.1) Information GatheringCottey College collects basic site use information that is not personally identifiable. This information might include: the operating system on your computer, the type of Web browser you are using, your IP address, and the links you followed to enter and leave our website.We or our business associates may use data collected on this site for Online Behavioral Advertising purposes, e.g. to customize ads to you on other websites as you browse the Web.  If you do not want your browsing behavior to be collected for Online Behavioral Advertising purposes, you may change your browser settings: Safari, Internet Explorer or Edge, Firefox , Chrome. You may also visit advertising sites directly to opt-out of ad targeting: AOL Advertising, APT from Yahoo!, Google, Microsoft Advertising, Yahoo!, AdRoll, Network Advertising Initiative.  Or, you may also wish to clear your web cache.   2) Commitment to Individual PrivacyAll personally identifiable information is collected on a voluntary basis, at the discretion of the website user. For example, it is your choice to provide your name, address or telephone number in the “Contact Us” section of the college’s website.3) Information UsageNon-personally identifiable information is used to help us improve our site by enabling us to discover and address the needs of our site visitors.It is Cottey’s policy to collect the least amount of personally identifiable information to fulfill the required tasks such as: your name, mailing address, email address and other contact information. This type of information is used for the purpose of responding to your requests for information about the college and to contact you about future products and services. Cottey College does not share personal information with third parties, apart from vendors who may utilize the information to perform services (e.g. credit card authorization, mail vendors, etc.).4) Browser CookiesA cookie is a small text file that may be used to collect information about website activity. Some cookies may serve to recall user information previously indicated by a Web user. Web browsers allow you to control cookies by not accepting them and even removing them from the system. Accepting the use of cookies will enhance your experience on our website.5) SecurityCottey intends to protect the security of personal information collected through its websites. Monetary transactions submitted through the website are encrypted using the Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL, protocol.6) Limitation of LiabilityThe Cottey College website may include hyperlinks to websites maintained or controlled by parties unaffiliated with Cottey College. Links to these websites are provided as a convenience only, and Cottey College is not responsible for and does not routinely approve, review or endorse the contents or use of any of the products or services that may be offered at those websites.7) European Union General Data Protection RegulationCottey College provides information on GDPR requirements and college processes.8) For More InformationYou may may view information related to other privacy concerns on our consumer information page. For further information about this document or to correct or modify any information collected through our website, please contact:Cottey College1000 W. Austin BlvdNevada, MO 64772(417) 667-8181
Share This Page:Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Reddit (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)Click to print (Opens in new window)
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
RSS SEO & Website Design By: KM Guru Marketing
Request Info
Degrees & Programs  Which degree program are you interested in?Please select...Bachelor of Science in Health SciencesBachelor of Science in BiologyBachelor of Arts in Women's StudiesBachelor of Arts in Secondary EducationBachelor of Arts in PsychologyBachelor of Arts in Organizational LeadershipBachelor of Arts in Liberal ArtsBachelor of Arts in International RelationsBachelor of Arts in International BusinessBachelor of Arts in Environmental StudiesBachelor of Arts in EnglishBachelor of Arts in CriminologyBachelor of Arts in Business Administration-ManagementAssociate in ScienceAssociate in Fine Arts-TheatreAssociate in Fine Arts-DanceAssociate in Fine Arts-ArtAssociate in Arts-MusicAssociate in ArtsStill DecidingPreferred Select...Please select...Preferred Start TermFall/AugustSpring/JanuaryPlease select...Preferred Start Year2021202220232024 Please fill out your contact info below:   First Name   Last Name Email Mobile
May we text you?YesNo When would you like to be contacted? EveningWeekend
Contact InformationYour Rights Under GDPR
